死亡飞车,世界上的头号运动
Death Race, the number one sport in the world,
位于终极岛
located on Terminal Island.
是一项历时三天 激烈的罪犯间的比赛
Convicts race over the course of three grueling days
为了赢得终极大奖
for the chance at the ultimate prize.
赢得5场比赛 你就可以赢得自由
Win five races, win your freedom.
现在预订下届死亡飞车
Preorder the next Death Race now
你不仅会得到20%的折扣,
and you'll not only get 20 % off,
你也将获得限量版的弗兰肯斯坦商品
but you'll also receive limited edition Frankenstein merchandise.
弗兰肯斯坦 这位连续四届死亡竞赛的冠军
Frankenstein, the four-time Death Race champion,
已经风靡全球
has taken the world by storm.
这位最不可能的英雄
The most unlikely of heroes
谁也不知道他从何而来
who has come out of nowhere
而现在他是唯一一个即将获得自由的人
and is now just one win away from freedom.
死亡飞车
Death Race.
现在现场直播中
Now streaming live.
死亡飞车是韦兰国际的商标
Death Race is the trademark of Weyland International.
你的安全是我们的首要任务
Your safety's our top priority.
今天弗兰肯斯坦赢得了他的第四场比赛
The notorious Death Racer known only as Frankenstein
臭名昭著的死亡飞车赛因此出名
won his fourth race today.
再赢一场这位蒙面杀手就会获得自由
One more victory and the masked killer gains his freedom.
弗兰肯斯坦什么也不怕
Frankenstein fears nothing.
韦兰
挡他道者死
Anything in his way, he destroys.
在我看 终极岛和死亡飞车的蓬勃发展
Under my watch, Terminal Island and Death Race have thrived.
谣言已经传到韦兰国际
Rumors have been going around that Weyland International,
这个死亡飞车背后的组织
the organization behind Death Race,
已经成为恶性收购的目标
has been targeted for hostile takeover.
作为一个企业家 谈到收购是很常见的
As a businessman, takeover talk is common.
韦兰
当你有价值连城的东西时 很自然的 人们想要拿走它
You have something of value,naturally,people want to take it away.
英国亿万富翁 奈尔斯·约克
British billionaire, Niles York,
奈尔斯·约克
已经将自己置于风暴中心
has placed himself in the center of a firestorm.
好吧 对此我没有什么想说的
Well, I've got nothing to say about that at the moment.
奈尔斯·约克
但是 我要说的是
But I will say this.
当我想得到什么东西的时候 没有人可以阻止我
When I want something, no one can stop me from taking it.
奈尔斯·约克
我没太在意 我获胜的战斗比我失败的多
I'm not too concerned. I've won more battles than I've lost.
我对韦兰感到遗憾 真的
I feel bad for Weyland, I really do.
奈尔斯·约克
人到中年 他已经是个老男人了
But Father Time, he's caught up with the old man.
他永远都没有机会了
He never really stood a chance.
死亡飞车3
地狱烈焰
早上好 韦兰先生
Good morning, Mr. Weyland.
也不是很糟糕 不是吗?
Wasn't so bad, was it?
我创立了这个公司
I built this business.
我没有输
I didn't have to steal it.
你留下的烂摊子 我来收拾 我可什么也没偷
What you left vulnerable, I seized. I stole nothing.
韦兰 你缺乏远见 这就是你的败笔
You lacked vision, Weyland. That was your undoing.
远见
Vision.
这就是你为什么要投资百万在世界各地的破监狱?
Is that why you're investing millions in dilapidated prisons all around the globe?
远见?
Vision?
你太没头脑了 你还是被埋在地下6英尺好
You're so far over your head, you might as well be six feet under the ground.
监狱业务并不能让公司盈利
The prison business is not what made this company profitable.
所以得出的结论是...
So the conclusion to draw,
你想独营死亡飞车
you're trying to franchise Death Race.
这是行不通的
It's not going to work.
因为你不能使它运行
Because you couldn't make it work.
我来告诉你什么是真正的眼光
Let me show you what true vision really looks like.
韦兰,你开创了一些美好的东西
You started something beautiful, Weyland.
但你那只是些皮毛
But you only scratched at the surface.
卡拉哈里最高戒备监狱
你说的对 我要将死亡飞车全球化
And you're right. I'm taking Death Race global.
明年的这个时候 每两周就有一次不同的比赛
By this time next year, there will be a different race every two weeks
赛道
不同的车手、赛道和挑战 会让你有一种不同的异国情调
at a different exotic hellhole with different drivers, tracks and challenges.
我会垄断这个地球上的历史以来最赚钱的运动
I will have a monopoly on the most profitable sport in the history of the planet.
更多的汽车 更多的欺诈 更多的枪支
More cars. More cons. More guns.
更多的死亡 只要想得到 没有做不到
More death. The sky's the limit.
好吧 你忘记了一件事情
Well, you forgot one thing.
弗兰肯斯坦
Frankenstein.
只是一个蒙面人而已
It's a man in a mask.
我可以将20个弗兰肯斯坦遍布全球
I could have 20 Frankensteins around the globe.
那粉丝们如何知道哪一个是真的?
How would the fans know which one was real?
弗兰肯斯坦今天赢得了他的第四场比赛
Frankenstein won his fourth race today.
再赢一场 他就能获得自由
One more win, he goes free.
这是每个粉丝都知道的事实
That's a fact that every fan knows.
现在 你如果改变游戏规则
Now, if you suddenly change the rules of the game,
你将失去你的观众
you're going to lose your audience.
而且如果你希望弗兰肯斯坦输的话
And if you're hoping that Frankenstein loses,
好吧 小子 我想这是第一次
well, son, I guess there's a first time.
现在 不用招牌明星
Now, how would your little copycat event play
你怎么玩转这个山寨小游戏?
without the game's marquee star?
这就是你为什么会注定失败
That's why you're going to fail.
你平时抽什么雪茄 韦兰?
What kind of cigars you smoke, Weyland?
当死亡飞车取得全球性成功时 我会送你一箱
I'll be sure to send you a box when Death Race becomes a global success.
这将是我第二次打败你 第二次你也输了
It'll be the second time I've beaten you. The second time you've lost.
好吧 趁你还能得瑟的时候赶紧吧
Well, you enjoy your moment while you can.
扯蛋的回报 小子
Payback's a bitch, son.
韦兰说的对
Weyland's right.
找出这个面具男
Find out who the man behind the mask really is.
看他喜欢什么 讨厌什么 想要什么
What he loves, what he hates, what he covets most.
然后查出韦兰在计划什么
And find out what Weyland was planning next.
你的意思是?
What do you mean?
该公司在售卖弗兰肯斯坦商品
The company's banking nearly eight million quid a week
一周经营近800万英镑
hawking Frankenstein merchandise.
他不会就此罢手的
He wasn't just gonna let it go.
还有别的吩咐吗?
Anything else?
对了 穿点像样的衣服 你看起来像个流浪的女子
Yeah. Get yourself some decent clothes.You look like a bag lady.
我爱死亡飞车了 不然我不会在这 也不会做这些事
I wouldn't be here, I wouldn't have done all this unless I absolutely loved Death Race.
所以我要对世界各地的百万计的粉丝们说
So I'm speaking to the millions of fans around the globe.
不要害怕 我和你们一样
Fear not. I am like you.
对于我们崇敬的 我不会破坏也不求妥协
I seek not to destroy nor to compromise what we've all come to revere.
我们所知所爱的死亡飞车是不会改变的
The Death Race that we all know and love will not change.
我保证它将发展壮大
It will grow bigger and better. This, I promise.
谢谢
Thank you.
一句话 我得说情况还好
Overall, I have to say I'm very happy.
你想看看吗?
You wanna take a look?
不
No.
明天我们将做几个测试
We'll run a few more tests tomorrow,
你会很快恢复原貌
and you're back to your old self in no time.
不 他不会的
No, he won't.
他会好的
He'll be better.
都出去
Everybody out.
你们听到那人说的了 喝杯咖啡休息一下
You heard the man. Take a coffee break, guys.
如此看来 我想传言是真的
So, I guess the rumors are true.
是的 我想你不会为我而流泪的
Yeah, and I guess you won't be shedding any tears for me.
嘿 你和我 还有卡尔 我们在一生中有着非比寻常的经历
Hey, you and I, Carl, we've taken very different paths in life.
但是我们都坚持走到了现在
But we both ended up here.
不 我在这儿
No, I'm here.
你想来就来 找你爱的人
You come and go as you please, see the ones you love.
他们看见你了
They see you.
别和我们比 韦兰 你失去了伙伴
Don't compare us, Weyland. You lost the company.
- 我输掉了我的一生  - 嗯 嗯
- I lost my life. - Mmm-hmm.
嗯 我还是收拾了你的烂摊子 助你脱离困境
Yeah, and I also fixed your face and I gave you a way out.
看着我 告诉我你会信守的承诺
Look at me and tell me you were gonna keep your word.
我并不是傻子 韦兰
I'm not stupid, Weyland.
你不是好心替我收拾烂摊子的 对吧?
And you didn't fix my face out of the kindness of your heart, did you?
那有传染性 我当时就快要死了
It was infected. I was gonna die.
你会失去你的明星车手
And you would have lost your star driver.
嗯 你没有那么糟糕 你是更糟糕
Yeah, you're not so bad. You're worse.
你想要我相信你?
And you want me to trust you?
你真该被破口大骂
You deserve the shit-storm you're in.
好吧 我有些消息给你 卡尔
Well, I got news for you, Carl.
你已经深陷其中了
You're already in waist-deep.
你是弗兰肯斯坦
You're Frankenstein.
这一切是你造成的
This all starts and ends with you.
卡尔·卢卡斯
Carl Lucas.
流氓出身
Born a gangster,
发展成为罪犯
became a prisoner,
现在成了怪物
and now, a monster.
也许他安息了
May he rest in peace.
你和你的团队赢5场
You and your team win five races
你就自由了
and you go free.
高博,雷斯特
Goldberg, Lists
还有那美丽的 美丽的卡特里娜
and that beautiful, beautiful Katrina.
现在 为此工作吧
Now, for this to work,
你不能告诉任何人你的真实身份
you can't tell your true identity to anyone.
卡尔·卢卡斯不存在
Carl Lucas stays dead.
你是弗兰肯斯坦
You're Frankenstein.
好吧 不客气 蠢蛋
Well, you're welcome, asshole.
即使赢4场 都不会谢你
Four wins and not even a thank you.
这一切都是为你而做
This all starts and ends with you.
是他 就是他
There he is. There's the guy.
我要转移你
I'm having you transferred.
你肯定听说在南非的卡拉哈里沙漠最高戒备监狱
You're headed to the Kalahari Desert Maximum Security Penitentiary
在那儿 你将参加有史以来第一次沙漠死亡飞车竞赛
in South Africa where you will compete in the first ever Desert Death Race.
哇哦 我能得到什么 我自己的沙漠越野车?
Wow. What do I get, my own dune buggy?
你只是借卡拉哈里监狱
You're just on loan to the Kalahari
去帮助他们开始第一轮的国际死亡飞车比赛
to help launch the first of what will be many international Death Races.
还有14K 当然还有你的团队
We're sending 14K, as well as both your teams.
那我建议 我要得到我的新护照
So I'm guessing I should get my passport updated.
我有种感觉 觉得你跟我说的不是真的
I get the feeling that you are not taking me seriously.
那是因为我不是
That's because I'm not.
听我说 我和韦兰有个交易
Listen to me. I made a deal with Weyland.
我再赢一场 我 我的团队
I win one more race, me, my team,
我们就出局
we're out.
嗯 你知道的 韦兰让人很遗憾
Yeah, well, you know, it's a pity about Weyland,
因为和他的一切交易都是无效的
because all deals with him are null and void.
你现在为我工作 新规
You work for me now. New rules.
不
No.
不 我不这么认为
No, I don't think so.
你别无选择 如果你不开的话
You don't have a choice, mate.But if you don't want to drive,
那好
fine.
我就用你的血来喷红我的飞机
I will paint my plane red with your blood.
真的吗?
Really?
奈尔斯?
Niles?
你想做什么 替换掉我?
What are you gonna do, replace me?
用谁？
With who?
为什么你会在意？ 你已经是个废人了
Why would you care? You're already dead.
这么说在你飞黄腾达时 你会有着明星般的待遇
So, as long as you're alive, you'll be treated like the star that you are.
或者
Or,
我可以简单地搞翻你的小飞机
I could just simply fuck up your little plan,
如果我不那么做 再赢一场比赛
couldn't I, by winning one more race
我就自由了
and I'm free.
哇 你可不能到达终点线 伙计
Wow. You'll never make it to the finish line, mate.
相信我
Trust me on that.
你输则活 赢则死
You lose, you live. You win, you die.
南非
好吧 滚出去!
Okay, get out!
我们走 快走!
Let's go, move!
把手提钻拿过来
Bring that jackhammer here.
站到队伍里来!快走！
Get in the line! Get moving!
小子 看看那些东西!
Boy, take a look at those!
快走！
Move your fuckin' arse.
那是谁?
Who's that?
嘿 高博!
Hey, Goldberg!
是的 是他
Yeah, that's right.
我特喜欢他 但是我们这里也是麻烦多多啊
I'm a big fan. But we've got our own bitches down here.
我不知道你为什么还带着你自己的
I don't know why you brought yours along.
嘿 我给你签个名吧
Hey, let me give you an autograph.
闪开！闪开！
Move! Move!
我们赶紧赶路吧
Let's take this fucking joint!
杀死他们!
Kill them all!
- 建立防线  - 建立防线,快！
- Set up a perimeter now. - On the ground, now!
靠!
Shit!
起来!
Get up!
你受伤了吗?什么?
Are you hurt? What?
卢卡斯 一直都是你
Lucas. It always was you.
你个婊子养的!
You son of a bitch!
我们都以为你死了
We thought you were dead.
看来你一直带着面具 对吧
So it's always been you behind the mask.
是的 一言难尽啊
Yeah, it's a long story.
那你和他们达成了什么协议?
So what kind of deal did they make, huh?
我别无选择
I didn't have a choice.
不管什么协议 肯定包括整容你的脸
Whatever it was, it included getting your face fixed.
我看到了 我在场
I saw it. I was there.
你在场 高博?
Did you, Goldberg?
还是 你只是看到了他们想要你看到的东西
Or did you just see what they wanted you to see?
他们想要我们看到什么?
What did they want us to see?
那不算协议
That is no deal.
你不需要达成协议
You never needed to make a deal.
你只要连续赢5次 就可以获得自由
All you had to do was win five races in a row and you're free.
那就是规则
Those are the rules.
牢笼里没有规则 雷斯特
There are no rules in the cage, Lists.
至少没有让牢笼受益的规则
At least none that benefit the cage.
相信你会得到你想要的 高博
Believe what you want, Goldberg.
我认为让他们看到我们在一起是不明智的决定
But I don't think it's wise, right now, that they see us together.
欢迎来到地狱
Welcome to hell.
快走 不要停下 快点
Keep moving, don't stop! Come on!
快点 快点 快点
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
欢迎来到卡拉哈里监狱 你要胆敢逃跑
Welcome to Kalahari Prison. You dare try and escape,
不劳我们动手 你会死在荒漠里 快点 快走!
the desert will kill you before we do. Come on, move!
你还好吗?
You all right?
关上门
Close the gate.
嘿 高博
Hey, Goldberg.
她现在更强壮了 也更好了
She's bigger and better.
远比之前强壮和优秀了
Way bigger. Way better.
在我十岁时 便经历了比大多数人
I've been through more shit in my life
一生经历的都多的倒霉事
than most people go through in 10.
但我从没撒谎 也没有背叛我的朋友
But what I never did was lie or betray my friends.
我不管你的意图是什么,
Doesn't matter what your intentions were,
我们不会散布你的秘密
your secret would have been safe with us.
我们本来可以帮上忙的
We could've helped.
你深知这一切
You know better than that.
帮助我是要付出代价的 所以我不打算让你这么做
Helping me comes with a price, and I wasn't about to let you do that.
你相信诅咒?
You believe in curses?
是这个
This thing.
它不会凭空而来
It comes with one.
你可以相信我们
You should've trusted us.
我们走 雷斯特
Let's go, Lists.
直播地点在南非的卡拉哈里监狱
Live from Kalahari Prison in South Africa,
死亡之路航海战争
this is Death Race Navigator Wars.
描述了16个最美丽
Featuring 16 of the most beautiful,
无情和对生命有致命打击性的女人
ruthless and lethal convicts alive,
包括一个恐怖分子和一个职业杀手
including an IRA terrorist, a contract killer,
甚至还有长相一样的双胞胎杀人恶魔
even identical twin serial killers.
但是人们都会将目光投到卡特里娜·班克斯
But all eyes will be on Katrina Banks,
臭名昭著的弗兰肯斯坦的优秀副驾驶员
the gorgeous copilot of the notorious Frankenstein.
这是死亡竞争 唯一的真理 活着
This is a match to the death. The only rule, survive.
到底发生了什么?
What the hell is happening?
莎塔娜
卡拉哈里死亡竞赛
创始人兼主持人
晚上好 欢迎来到这一次特殊的死亡竞赛
Good evening and welcome to a special pre-Death Race event.
十六个美丽而致命的女人
Sixteen beautiful, yet deadly women,
夺取死亡竞赛航海家的10个名额
vie for 10 spots as Death Race navigators.
他们将与死神较量 看看谁值得
These ladies will battle to the death to see who's worthy
在明天的死亡竞赛中掌舵
to navigate in tomorrow's Death Race.
三分钟后
After the first three minutes,
压力板即将激活各种致命的武器
pressure plates activate a variety of lethal weapons.
战争结束 只有10个人会活着离开
The fight ends when 10 ladies are left alive.
卡特里娜活着出去的概率很低
Katrina's statistical probability of survival is very low.
瑞典双胞胎不会自相残杀
And the Swedish twins aren't gonna fight each other.
只有卡特丽娜的声望会吸引更多的关注
Plus, Katrina's celebrity will attract more attention.
那样会有改变结果的可能性
That changes the odds.
你在说什么?
So, what are you saying?
百分之七到百分之十的概率
Seven to 10 %.
最好的情况下
Best case scenario.
调暗灯光 大屠杀要开始了
Dim the lights. The carnage is about to begin.
卡特里娜,踹她!
Katrina, kick some ass!
我了解我的观众喜欢看什么
Do I know my audience or what?
操蛋的电视真人秀 来吧
That's reality TV shit. Come on.
好的
Yes.
现在激活压力板
Pressure plates are now active.
跟紧点  跟紧点
Go in tighter. Go in tighter.
给我个特写!
Get me a close-up!
杀!
Kill!
你想要点爆米花吗?
Do you want some popcorn with that?
不需要
I don't need...
去拿武器, 卡特里娜!
Get to the weapons, Katrina!
来吧 好好教训她!
Come on, cook her ass!
5号摄像机 特写! 卡特里娜·班克斯
Camera five, close-up! Katrina Banks.
我弄死你!
I'm gonna fuck you up!
拿好这个
Take this!
干得好!干得好
Good work, good work!
当心
Watch out!
你爱死我了!
You love me to death!
不
No!
哦 老兄 我真以为双胞胎姐妹都会成功的
Oh, man, I really thought both twins were gonna make it,
他们还大肆宣扬她们的  你知道吧?
the way they hyped 'em up and all, you know?
不要相信大肆宣扬
Never believe your own hype.
不要错过那个机会!
Don't miss that shot!
只有十个人会活下来 作为航海家参加明天的死亡竞赛
Ten women remain who'll compete as navigators in tomorrow's Death Race.
参加战斗的人都是重犯
Fighters are convicted violent felons. Acts should not be duplicated at home.
放轻松点 普鲁登斯 这儿没什么好怕的
Relax, Prudence. There's nothing for you to fear here.
他们可能是邪恶无情的谋杀犯或者强奸犯
They may be ruthless, vicious murderers and rapists,
他们经历了太多 足够无视你
but they've taste enough to ignore you.
竞赛时间到 混蛋们!
It's race time, motherfuckers!
不要碰我 今天早晨我感到有点不舒服
Don't touch me. I'm feeling a little fragile this morning.
快点 我们走
Come on, let's go.
快点!
Come on!
我也很高兴见到你
Good to see you, too.
去死吧
Drop dead.
- 快点！- 好主意 但我已经尝试过了
Come on, move! Good idea. But I already tried that.
下一个!
Next!
下一个入队
Next in line.
下一个!
Next!
不错 谢谢
Nice. Thank you.
下一个 继续!
Another one. Next!
为什么把这东西放我身体里？
What do you think you're putting inside of me?
放开他 他只是在做他该做的事情
Let him go. He's just doing what he's told to do.
跟夺命岛不同 这里没有墙
Unlike Terminal Island, there are no walls here.
我们不想让车手们为了自由胡乱冲撞
We didn't want our drivers dashing for their freedom.
它会随时定位你们
This will tell us exactly where you are at all times.
那么如果我偏离航线 会怎样呢?
So, I go off-course, what happens?
你对德国制造的红外线智能彩虹导弹还不是太熟悉?
You're not familiar with the German-made Iris-T Infra-red Smart missile?
是的
No.
你想偏离航线
You go off-course, and you will be.
就像在卡拉哈里没有逃跑的机会
Just as there's no escape from Kalahari,
死亡竞赛也没有机会逃跑
there is no escape from Death Race.
好吧 没事吧?
Well, ain't that somethin'?
奈尔斯先生 只要你在这里 我听你指挥
Mr. York. While you are here, I want you to know that I am at your disposal.
你心里想的任何事情
Anything your heart desires, consider yours.
任何事情?
Anything?
请坐
Please do take a seat.
直播现场位于南非卡拉哈里监狱
Streaming live from the Kalahari Prison in South Africa,
这里全都是世界上独一无二的暴徒份子
home to the most ruthless and violent criminals the world has ever seen.
奈尔斯亲临死亡竞赛
Niles York presents Death Race.
11个参赛者将进行为时超过3天残酷的竞争
Eleven drivers will compete over three brutal days
跨越地球上最险恶的领土
across one of the most dangerous terrains on Earth
只为最后的奖励
for a chance at the ultimate prize.
赢5次竞赛 获取自由
Win five races, win your freedom.
雷斯特?
Lists?
这里有话筒和扩音器 但没有耳机了
There's a speaker and mic here, so no more headsets.
武器的扳机还在原来的地方
But the weapon trigger's still in the same place.
好的
Okay.
没有防御武器
There are no shields out here.
只有攻击性武器
Only offensive weapons.
地图上标有武器的位置 碑石上刻着呢
Weapon locations are marked on the map, indicated here on the tablet.
现在 记住 你必须穿越而不是直接开过去 才能激活它
Now, remember, you have to drive through, not over, to activate.
你认为这像巴哈竞赛吗?
You think this thing's gonna be like a Baja race?
关于巴哈 我只知道
The only thing I know about Baja,
他是我喜欢的一种炸玉米饼
it's a style of tacos I like.
高博
Goldberg,
这次我需要你的帮助
I'm gonna need you on this one.
我会的
I got your back.
你要考虑三件事情
Three things you gotta worry about.
罗斯
Razor.
为了获胜 他甚至会杀了我们
He'd rather kill us than win.
尼禄
Nero.
方格旗与获胜无关紧要
Checkered flag has nothing to do with winning.
好的 那么第三件事?
Okay. So what's the third?
第三
Third,
就是坐在你旁边的女孩
it's that beautiful girl sitting next to you.
让我们准备好在线直播吧
Let's get it ready for an online broadcast.
我们做个紧凑的微控制器15号、10号和8号摄像机
Let's make a tight MCU. Camera 15, 10 and eight.
谢谢
Thanks.
明白了
Gotcha.
卡特里娜
Katrina.
别 我不想听你说
Don't. I don't wanna hear it.
你是我的副手 你能说英语吗?
You're my nav-girl. You, do you speak English?
我说英语 你个傻子
I speak English, you fucking idiot.
让我们赢得这场比赛吧
Let's just fucking win this race.
哇 非常棒
Wow, this is gonna be great.
乔科
Joker
第一次正式比赛于1967年10月31日
The first official race of this kind
在加利福尼亚半岛的提华纳举行
started in Tijuana, Baja California on October 31st, 1967
比赛叫 墨西哥诺拉1000公路赛车会
and was called the NORRA Mexican 1000 Rally.
那年比赛的总长度为849英里合计1366公里,
The course length that year was 849 miles, or 1 ,366 kilometers,
终点为南加利福尼亚的拉帕兹
and ended in La Paz, Baja California Sur, sir.
最终的获胜者用时为27小时38分钟
The overall winning time was 27 hours, 38 minutes
由威尔逊和特德创造
set by Vic Wilson and Ted Mangels
开的是迈尔斯·马恩越野车
while driving a Meyers Manx buggy.
你在和谁说话?
Who're you talking to?
我以为你会欣赏有关的历史展望呢
Thought you'd appreciate some relative historical perspective.
嗯 你想错了
Well, you thought wrong.
设置灯光
Set the lights.
10号机 左拐
Number 10, pan to your left.
所有的目光都注视着弗兰肯斯坦 他试着取得第五场胜利
All eyes are on Frankenstein,as he tries to win his fifth race
成为第一个获得自由的人
and become the first inmate to win his freedom.
神奇的弗兰肯斯坦在赢得第四场比赛后
The mysterious Frankenstein became a worldwide phenomenon
成为全球著名的天才
after winning his first four Death Races.
但是那是在终极岛
But that was back on Terminal Island.
他在南非能成功吗?
Can he repeat that success here in Africa?
Three.
独一无二的挑战摆在我们车手面前
Unique challenges lay ahead as our drivers
他们通过了终极岛的重重考验
move from the confines of Terminal Island's track onto three desert courses.
Two.
残杀即将开始
The carnage is about to begin.
你他妈的在做什么?
What the fuck are you doing?
他犯规了
He's jumping.
有犯规的
We've got a jumper.
开火
Fire away.
我们的追踪器怎么办?
What about our trackers?
你知道什么?
You know something?
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
快闪开!
Get out of here, man!
它来了！它来了
It's coming, it's coming!
噢 天啊！你在干什么！
Oh, my God, what are you doing?
它在这儿 就在这儿 就在这儿
It's here, it's here, it's here.
杰克尔成为第一个被淘汰的人
And The Jackal becomes a Death Race first.
以前还没有人在比赛开始前就死掉了
Never before has a driver been killed before the race has even begun.
重置灯光
Reset lights.
蠢货
Stupid.
太搞笑了
That's entertainment.
但是对我们来说非常好
Well, that worked well. For us.
出发
Go.
Go
启动! 启动!
Start! Start!
耶! 狗娘养的
Yippee ki-yay, motherfucker!
哇!
Whoa!
看看那鸟人!
Look at the fuckers!
介绍奥加尔·布莱恩
Introducing Olga Braun.
- 想我来开吗? - 去 那是...
- Do you want me to drive? - Fuck, it's...
死亡飞车赛的第一位女车手
Death Race's first ever female driver.
耶! 来吧
Yeah! Come on.
启动!启动!启动!
Start! Start! Start!
你个怪胎
You're a freak.
噢耶！
Oh, yeah.
疯子
Psycho
嘿 高博 你找到我了吗? 在线吗?
Hey, Goldberg. You getting me? You online?
你现在准备就绪了吗?
Are you ready to get serious now?
路非常窄 所以只能在弯道超车
The roads are narrow, so pass only on the turns.
25英里标志前 不可使用武器
Weapons are inactive until mile marker 25.
雷斯特 我们的最高速度是多少?
Lists, what's my top speed on this thing?
每小时100公里 但是你在某些地方需要保持50-60的时速
100 miles per hour, but you wanna keep it somewhere between 50 and 60.
忘记你对比赛所知的一切
Forget everything you know about racing.
沙漠赛车与速度无关
Desert racing isn't about speed.
这是耐力和操纵
It's about endurance and handling.
等下 我觉得你对这比赛一无所知
Hang on a minute. I thought you didn't know shit about this kind of racing
我不知道 这东西是第一次在谷歌上出现
I don't. It's the first thing that came up on Google.
比赛者第一次涉足这样的比赛
The racers enter the first leg of the race,
穿越卡巴沙漠
the sand dunes of Katbakkies Pass.
他就在你后面!
He's right behind you!
嘿 别开得像个二逼
Hey, stop driving like a pussy.
在我们家乡 女人都比你开得好
Where I'm coming from, the ladies,they can drive better than this.
- 右急转 - 什么时候?
- Turn hard right.- When?
现在!
Now!
你他妈的想开?
You wanna fucking drive?
你能闭嘴吗?
Could you just not talk?
- 别说话 - 闭嘴
- Just don't talk.- Shut up.
卢克 你得找到武器的标志
Luke! You need to find the weapon marker again.
操
Fuck!
太他妈的棒了!
That was fucking great!
- 我看到右边有武器标志了  - 嗯 我看到了
- I see weapon markers on the right. - Yeah, I see it.
正前方有跟踪标志
You see the tracking markers straight ahead.
你以为我是瞎子吗?
You think I'm blind?
草你大爷的
Fuck off, man.
弗兰肯斯坦!
Frankenstein!
混账！
Motherfucker!
罗斯的武器启动了
Razor's weapons are activated!
来吧 换大炮 换环形炮
Come on, turn the cannon, turn the cannon around.
开快点!
Go faster!
给他们看看咱们的厉害
We have to show them how it's done.
你不采取些措施吗?
Are you gonna take this shit?
耶耶耶 中国你搞定了吗?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. China. Did you get that, China?
让他们进来 进来
Turn them in. Turn them in.
爽啊!
Yeah!
启动大炮
Activate the cannon.
大炮启动
Cannon activated.
乔科用大炮对准了你
Joker's got a cannon trained on you.
小心 你的背后!
Look out! Behind you!
让我送这狗崽子上西天
Let's light this puppy up.
拜 拜 拜
Bye, bye, bye.
来吧!
Come on!
干掉他
Fuck him up.
你还好吧 弗兰肯斯坦?
Are you okay, Mr. Frankenstein?
你知道什么?我从来没想过我会错过墓碑
You know what? I never thought I'd miss the Tombstone.
高博 我需要你的帮助
Goldberg. I need your help.
别摆脱他 让他就在你的右后方
Don't shake him off! Let him get right up behind you.
高博 你疯了吗?
Goldberg, are you crazy?
来吧!
Come on!
- 我讨厌这个混蛋  - 漂亮
- I'm getting sick of this bastard. - Oh, beautiful.
你的做法不合逻辑
What you're doing is illogical.
噢 天哪 那感觉真棒啊
Oh, God, that felt good.
这样我们可扛不了多久了
We can't take much more of this.
握稳方向盘 卢克 相信我!
Stay on the wheel, Luke. Trust me!
去你妈的笨蛋!
Fucking idiot!
现在笑谁 乔科?
Who's laughing now, Joker?
你知道 我告诉你的事情 我印象非常非常深刻
You know, I gotta tell you something.I am very, very impressed.
漂亮 高博
Nice, Goldberg.
去他妈的逻辑
Fuck logic.
有些时候你要跟着你的心走
Sometimes you just gotta let your heart and gut tell you what's right.
两个参赛者倒下了 还剩9个 现在进入卡雅利沙小镇
Two Death Racers down. Nine remain, as we enter Khayelitsha Township.
该死!
Damn!
该死
Shit.
左转 左边 左边
Go left, left, left, left, left.
启动武器就是为了这部分
Weapons activated for this sector only.
左转!
Take left!
这是非洲 婊子!
This is Africa, son of a bitch!
这些人就是在找死 滚出街道啊!
These people got a damn death wish. Off the fucking road!
狗娘养的!
Son of a bitch!
我们得离开这!
We need to get outta here!
不 待在车里 有跟踪装置!
No, stay with the car! The tracking device!
走吧 快点 跑
Let's go! Come on! Run!
有个逃跑者
We've got a runner.
谁?
Who?
帅气孩子离开了他的车
Pretty Boy's left his car.
我们锁定了他
We've got a lock on him.
开火
Fire.
他在城镇中 你要杀死无辜的人吗?
He's in the middle of a town. Won't you kill a lot of innocent people?
他们会在来生得到奖赏 准备好就开火
They will be rewarded in their next life. Fire when ready.
见鬼!
Shit!
滚开!
Out of my way!
操!
Fuck!
当心 当心
Watch out, watch out.
不!
No!
真他妈的精彩
Fucking beautiful.
- 他们来了 - 还剩7位车手
- They are coming here!  - Seven drivers remain,
他们进入最后的角逐
as they enter the last leg of stage one.
迷失地带
The lost zone.
该死!
Shit!
嘿 雷斯特 你对这些家伙了解吗?
Hey, Lists, do you know anything about these guys?
他们是卡拉哈里的军阀
They're the warlords of Kalahari.
他们制造了这一地区74.5%的犯罪案件
They're responsible for exactly 74.5 % of all organized crime in the region.
毒品 卖淫 绑架是他们盈利的3大方式
Drugs, prostitution, kidnapping are their three biggest earners.
好的 正是我们所需要的
Great, just what we needed.
别管他 卢克 完成比赛就行了
Let it go, Luke. Just finish the race.
妈的 这些人也参加比赛了吗?
Shit. Are these people even in the game?
他妈的 让开!
Just move out of my fucking way!
去他妈的14K!
This, fucking 14K!
他追上来了 在我们的后面 贱人！
He's coming up behind us. Bitch!
卢克 你在第二位 你必须超过罗斯
Luke, you're in second place. You have to pass Razor.
这是终点前的最后一个弯道 来吧 卢克!
You're on the last corner before the finish line. Come on, Luke, push!
- 罗斯第一名 - 该死
- Razor takes day one. - Damn!
弗兰肯斯坦紧随其后
Frankenstein finishing a close second.
14K 奥尔加 贝贝 疯子 尼禄 都幸存了
14K, Olga, Baby, Psycho and Nero have all survived.
太不可思议了 莎塔娜 难以置信的任务
That was amazing, Satana. Incredible job.
我想这值得庆贺 你觉得呢?
I think it's cause for a celebration, don't you?
普鲁登斯
Prudence.
滚出去 让其他人也滚出去
Fuck off and tell the rest of them to fuck off, too.
所有人都出去
Everybody out.
我说了 所有人都出去!
I said, everybody out!
快点 快 出去 都出去
Keep moving! Come on, get out, everybody!
嘿 你今天干得不错
Hey, you did well today.
你看 你现在想操我了吧 是不?你现在想操我了
You see, you wanna fuck me now don't you? You wanna fuck me now.
天哪 她现在想操我 典型啊
God, she wants to fuck me now. Typical.
你现在真的想操我吗?
Do you really wanna fuck me now?
卡特里娜  我知道乱糟糟的 还好吗?
Katrina. Look, I know I fucked up, okay?
我只是想保护你
I was just trying to protect you.
你知道了 对你不是好事
It wasn't safe for you to know.
我们不再是以前的我们了
We can't be what we were.
第二名 你懈怠了
Second place. You're slipping.
嗯
Yeah.
雷斯特 让这事过去吧
Lists, let's get this thing cleaned up.
弗兰肯斯坦!
Frankenstein!
噢 没门儿!
Oh, no fucking way!
他妈的是怎么回事?
What the hell is going on?
隧道之战  是弗兰肯斯坦
A fight in the tunnel. It's Frankenstein.
马上把他轰出去!
Get him out of there. Now!
马上 出去!
Now, get out!
医生 我们需要医生!
Doctor! We need a doctor!
医生!
Doctor!
乔治·威利斯 白金汉宫第一伯爵
George Villiers, 1st Duke of Buckingham, Crazy Horse,
法国的亨利三世 和亨利四世
Henry Ill of France, Henry IV of France.
我会没事吧?
Am I gonna be all right?
你会没事的
You're gonna be fine.
只是一点擦伤
It's just a scratch.
现在 你得脱下裤子
Now I'm gonna need you to drop your trousers.
必须那样吗?
Is that necessary?
什么?我会没事的吧?
What? Am I all right?
你会没事的
You're going to be fine.
也许我该开诚布公 我是你的超级粉丝
What I probably should have disclosed, I'm a big fan of yours.
有多超级?
How big?
歌手 作家斯密斯 当然 凯撒大帝
Singer songwriter Elliott Smith and, of course, Julius Caesar.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
我在罗列最让人伤心的值得注意的受害者
Well, I'm listing the most notable stabbing victims.
他会没事的
He's gonna be okay.
我去看看他
I gotta see him.
他怎么样了?
How is he?
很好
Wonderful.
作为女人 我想为弗兰肯斯坦提供点额外奖
As girls, I thought it would only be fitting to offer Frankenstein,
我们的新名人 激励 奖励
our new celebrity, an incentive, a prize,
免费干炮
a free fuck.
好的 亲爱的!
All right, honey!
安布尔 起来 弄弄他
Amber, get up, move it.
快点
Hurry up.
好了 美女!
Get it, girl!
跟你的男友说再见 宝贝儿
Say bye to your boyfriend, honey.
臭婊子!
Fucking bitch!
有人要操你男友了!
Someone's fucking your boyfriend!
一个礼物
A gift.
弗兰肯斯坦?
Frankenstein?
嗯
Yeah.
那么
So,
我想我们可以讨论下合同里的条款
I was hoping that we could discuss the terms of our contract.
我想跑6场 签3年的合同
I was thinking six races per year, three year guarantee.
- 哦 是吗?  - 是的
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
那你觉得多少?
And how much did you have in mind?
我让马提娜一起来出价
I got Martine to put together a bid.
哦 你这么做了 是吗?
Oh, you did, did you?
你在开玩笑吧?
You gotta be kidding, right?
我相信这是公平的
I believe that it's fair.
你知道什么? 等明天的结果出来了
Do you know what? Let's just see how this one concludes tomorrow
我们再来讨论未来的比赛吧
before we discuss any future races.
但是我得告诉你 我非常 非常乐意
But I gotta tell you, I am very, very pleased
告诉你事情将会怎样发展
with how things are going so far.
我认为那不容易
I didn't think it would be this easy.
你指的是什么?
What do you mean?
我希望和怪人一起 他们告诉我他是个怪物
I was expecting issues with the freak. They told me he was a monster.
他是只波斯猫
He's a pussycat.
别小看他
Do not underestimate him.
我和那家伙达成协议 我想和他重新协定 但是他不同意
I made a deal with the guy. I was expecting him to renegotiate. But he didn't.
他在计划些东西
He's planning something.
嗯
Hmm.
别再盯着我了 让我们和谐相处
Stop fucking me with your eyes and let's get on with this.
这儿怎么回事?
What the fuck is going on here?
你第一次看到白鬼裸女?
The first time you see a white nincompoop naked?
快点 走 他妈的 快点 该死
Come on, move! Damn it! Come on. Shit.
- 怎么了 宝贝 - 嘿
- What's up, baby? - Hey.
我们来吧
Let's do it.
卢卡斯呢?
Where's Lucas?
你在这里干嘛
What are you doing here?
真实时刻
Truth time.
我有我的原因
Look, I had my reasons.
可我没有坦诚的告诉你 我对此很抱歉
But I haven't been straight with you. And I'm sorry for that.
但是 我想让这进入正轨
But I wanna make this right.
嗯 那就不要再对我们撒谎了
Well, then don't lie to us again.
好吧 关于比赛 你们都必须知道
Okay. Look, there's something you all need to know about the race.
我和新老板达成协议
I did make a deal with the new boss.
故意求输
To lose.
求输? 那你在车里会很难熬的
To lose? You'll have a tough time losing in this car.
我知道 他用我的命做条件
I know. He had a gun to my head.
他用你们所有人的命做条件
He had a gun to all of your heads.
所以我答应了新的协议
So, I made a new deal.
这就是我们要做的
And this is what we're gonna do.
欢迎来到死亡飞车赛 还剩7名车手
Welcome to stage two of Death Race. Seven drivers remain.
就位 放松点 厮杀即将开始
Sit back, relax. The carnage is about to begin.
登陆并了解你最爱的车手
Log on and get inside access on your favorite drivers.
再花些钱 你就可以
For an additional cost, you can tap in
分别观看到车手车上的摄像头画面
to the closed circuit camera inside the driver's car.
死亡飞车赛
Death Race.
多么美好的一天
It's a beautiful day
适合去死
to die.
尼禄领先 弗兰肯斯坦紧跟其后
Nero is in the lead, followed by Frankenstein,
14K 罗斯 奥尔加
14K, Razor and Olga.
令人惊讶的 疯子第六 贝贝第七
The surprising Psycho is sixth. And Baby is seventh.
嗯 武器现在启动了 对吗?
So, weapons are active now, yes?
是还是不是呢 真让人纠结啊
Yes and no. There's a little twist.
噢!
Ooh!
车手们接近科斯路了 直通向干湖
The racers approach Keiskie Road, heading towards the dry lake.
看  他们给了你一个曲线球
Look, they're throwing you a curve ball.
那个武器标记是25英里的最后一个
That weapons marker you see is the last one for 25 miles.
第一个通过它会得到武器
First one through it gets the weapons.
但是 如果你死了 那个武器标记就重新激活了
But if you die, the weapon marker reactivates.
那样的话 大家都会灌你的肠
So, everyone's gonna be on your ass.
因为 如果我做了就很可恶 不做就要被骂 对吧?
It's because I'm damned if I do, damned if I don't, right?
你懂了 伙计 完全正确
You got it, homes. Exactly.
那是武器标记
There's the weapon marker.
武器标记在你的左边
Weapon marker's coming up on your left.
好的 那儿
Okay, over there.
卢克!
Luke!
近了 快到了 加油 加油!搞定他 太棒了
Almost, almost, come on! Come on, make it! Yes!
奥加尔赢得了武器标记
Olga wins the weapons marker.
操
Fuck it.
嘿 对不起 女士
Hey, sorry, ladies.
称不上女士
Those aren't ladies.
别嫉妒
Don't get jealous.
看着你的路
Get your eyes back on the road.
好的
Sure.
奥加尔领先
There's Olga, up ahead.
操!
Fuck!
婊子
Fucking bitch.
哦耶
Oh, yeah.
这也许不是个好主意
Maybe this wasn't such a good idea after all.
为什么?
Why?
因为他们现在都在我们后面了
'Cause they're all after us now.
操蛋!
Fuck this!
哥 你把这婊子弄走吧 快啊!
Man, you get the bitch out of the way. Come on!
我是个坏人
I'm a bad man.
爽呆了!
Oh, yeah!
哦，妈的!
Oh, shit!
耶!
Yeah!
把这个婊子打到外面去
Knock this bitch out the way.
亲亲你的屁屁
Kiss your fucking ass.
喔!
Whoo!
我告诉过你
I told you.
你现在怎么办?婊子！
What you gonna do, bitch?
你得到什么了?
What you got?
来啊 快点
Come on. Come on.
- 尝尝这个吧! - 哦！妈的！
- Eat this! - Oh, shit!
武器制标记在正前方
Weapon marker's dead ahead.
好的
Okay.
这场双杀的比赛只剩5位选手了
The double kill leaves only five cars in the race,
他们正驶进卡尔维亚小镇
as they head into Calvinia Township.
天啊 有人惹怒了他们 我认为他们很不友好
Jesus, somebody pissed them off. I don't think they're friends.
他们真的不怎么喜欢我们
They really don't like us.
是的 我已经习惯了
Yeah, I'm getting used to that.
你为什么不加热喷火器?
Why don't you warm up that flame thrower?
好主意!
Finally!
小心!
Watch out!
来吧!
Come on!
他妈的滚开
Fucking roll, will you?
哇!
Whoa!
天啊 太诡异了!
Holy shit, that's awesome!
好吧 就那样 嗯?
Okay. It's like that, huh?
该死!
Damn it!
操蛋的交火
Fucking fire.
好吧
All right.
狗娘养的!
Son of a bitch!
耶!
Yeah!
卢克 小心 罗斯来了
Luke! Watch, Razor's coming closer.
他跟上来了 在我们后面
He's coming up behind us.
想玩玩嘛?我们来个了断吧
Do you wanna play? Let's end this.
- 婊子  - 你妈的
- Bitch! - You fucker.
伙计 我讨厌这家伙
Man. I'm sick of this asshole.
我能看到你 魔鬼!
I can see you, devil!
什么?
What?
你干什么? 放开我
What the fuck are you doing? Get off me.
他妈的太精彩了
This is just so fucking beautiful.
尼禄被淘汰出局
And that marks the end of Nero.
进入最后一站 还剩4个人
As we enter the final stage, we're down to the final four.
驶过卢里斯方丹[南非一地名]到达终点
Driving back through Loeriesfontein to the finish line.
让我们看看卡拉哈里军阀会做些什么
Let's see what the warlords of Kalahari have in store today.
武器标记准备启动了
Weapon markers ready for activation.
好的 我们好了
Okay, we're clear.
立刻启动武器
Get me weapons now.
坚持住
Hang on.
他去哪? 我们还没有来个了断呢
Where's he going? We're not done yet.
你他妈的想干什么?
What the fuck you want?
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
嗯?
Huh?
谁做什么?
What's who doing?
你会死的!
You will die!
那样做为了啥?
What was that for?
为了保住你性命
To save your ass.
快 快 快
Go, go, go.
我们有伙伴了
We got company.
该死!
Shit!
2号机 跟上
Camera two, pick that up.
狗娘养的!
Motherfucker!
这些人是谁?
Who the fuck are these people?
没事儿 我来搞定
It's okay. I got it.
在你的后面
Coming up behind you.
去死吧 你个野种!
Die, you bastard!
这太不可思议了
This is just fucking awesome.
是啊
Yeah.
你跑不掉的 贱货!
You can't run, motherfucker!
接近了
This is gonna be close.
现在怎么办 卢克?
What now, Luke?
可以了
It's on.
2号机 近拍
Camera two, pan in.
2号机 近点!
Camera two, move it!
别错过镜头 伙计们 快
Let's not lose that shot, boys. Come on.
动起来 动起来 你想错过这个镜头吗?
Move it, move it. Do you wanna miss the fucking shot?
了不起
Awesome.
第二天的结果太出乎预料了
Day two concludes with a bang.
明天将会是史诗般的时刻
Tune in tomorrow for the epic conclusion.
任何转播或者未授权使用都会被死亡惩罚
Any rebroadcast or unauthorized use is punishable by death,
如果年龄低于15岁 就会有牢狱之灾
or life in prison if under the age of 15.
我不知道他有孩子
I didn't know he had a child.
我们对身边的人了解如此之少感到震惊
Shocking how little we know about the ones closest to us.
我秘书几乎没有不知道
I know virtually nothing about my secretary here.
她知道我生活的各个方面
Conversely, she knows every aspect of my life,
私人的 商业的 好的 坏的 邪恶的
personal, business, good, bad and ugly.
转过来看着我
Turn around and face me.
关于高博 我很抱歉
I'm sorry to hear about Goldberg.
我不了解他 但是我知道他对你整个团队的重要性
I never knew the man, but I know how integral he was to your team.
你这样的人能知道这些真让人不解
What possible understanding can a man like you know about that?
他不只是我团队的一部分 他胜似亲人
He was more than just a part of my team. He was family.
嗯
Hmm.
清醒点 我们的协议依然有效 对吗?
Just to be clear, our deal still stands. Yes?
现在 别让你的情绪扰乱了你的判断
Now, don't let your emotions cloud your judgment.
14K明天会赢
14K will win tomorrow.
你们失控了 官方会说 机械故障导致了你们失败
You're gonna stall out. Officially, mechanical failure resulted in your loss.
我不想让它看起来是正常的打败你
I don't want it to look like you were beat.
我们不会破坏你的名声
Can't damage your rep now, can we?
清楚吗?
Are we clear?
我提问时 你应该回答我 明白吗?
When I ask you a question, you answer me. Do you understand?
不 不完全明白
No. Not really.
现在把那些有关取胜的愚蠢想法 抛出你的脑海
Now get these foolish thoughts of winning out of your head.
你明天就会输 要么帮我
You will lose tomorrow, or so help me God,
要么就把你放到我能找到的最阴森 最黑暗的监狱里
I will put you in the deepest, darkest cell I can find.
当你在那儿为毫无生气的生活哭泣时
And while you're down there, crying about that dead spic,
想象一下我会怎么对待你的女友吧
just imagine what I'll be doing to your girlfriend.
- 稀烂  - 你要怎样?
- Bad idea. - What are you gonna do?
- 威胁我杀了我吗?  - 不
- Threaten to kill me? - No.
不 奈尔斯
No, Niles.
那会让你解脱的太容易了
That would be letting you off too easy.
你可以活到明天 但是你不能赢
You can live tomorrow, but you can't win.
也许吧 你应该考虑一下和谐问题 像其他人一样
Maybe. Guess you'll just have to tune in, huh? Like everybody else.
不不不 我需要私下谈谈
No, no, no, no. I need to talk in private.
我听得见
I hear you.
你想和我说些什么吗?
Is there something you wanna say to me?
我只是想知道
I was just wondering
你是不是原版的弗兰肯斯坦
if you are the original Frankenstein.
为什么不是呢?
And why is that?
想想吧
Think about it.
带面具那个人是谁?
Who is the man behind the mask?
嗯?有人知道吗?
Hmm? Does anybody know?
他们只是怪物
They just want the monster.
他们用这样的方式把你带出去 杀死一个普通人
And they can take you out in a way that would kill a normal human being,
然后找人来顶替 天哪
and then just slap the suit on the next guy and hey, presto.
弗兰肯斯坦还活着
Frankenstein lives.
你认为他们会杀了我?
You think they're gonna kill me?
不 弗兰肯斯坦永生
No. Frankenstein can never die.
他可以被枪杀 他可以玉石俱焚 他可以爆炸
He can be shot. He can crash and burn. He can explode.
弗兰肯斯坦总是可以摆脱困境
But Frankenstein will always emerge.
也许颓废而且带着伤 但是总是活着
Battered and bruised, maybe. But alive.
让他的传奇再伟大点儿
Just makes his legend even greater.
是的是的 他跟我说过话
Yes. Yes, he spoke to me.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
这是什么意思?
What is the meaning of this?
这是我的事
This is my business.
这是我的成果
This is my production.
不 这是我的成果 我的!
No, this is my production. Mine!
你的电台根本都不愁卖了 现在你出局
And your network was more than eager to sell it and you out.
我觉得你现在投标都不需要了
Guess you won't be needing that bid now.
为此 我会给你免费通过
I'll give you a free pass for that one.
但是如果你还想有这种事
But if you try anything like it again,
我会把你禁闭起来 然后亲自为你挑选
and I will have you chained up and I personally will pimp you out
这个监狱里最讨厌的人 陪你度过
to the nastiest fucking psychos in this prison.
嘿 你 停下
Hey, you, stop.
警卫
Guard.
让他过去
Let her through.
你们所有的人 离开我们
All of you. Leave us.
我想我们唯一能为弗兰肯斯坦提供的就是
I thought it would only be fitting to offer Frankenstein,
我们的新名人 激励 奖励
our new celebrity, an incentive, a prize,
免费干炮
a free fuck.
这么说 你
So did you...
和她上床了?
Sleep with her?
没
No.
而你知道我为什么没有 对吧?
And you know why I didn't. Right?
嘿 你 回去工作!
Hey, you. Get back to work!
走
Go.
我不会让你失望的
I won't let you down.
虽然我没有任何数据来支持这种说法
Though I don't have any statistical evidence to back up that statement,
我强烈地感觉到...
I feel strongly...
雷斯特 没人 没人让我如此的信任
Lists, there's no one, no one I'd rather have watching my back.
谢谢 卢克
Thanks, Luke.
你介意吗?
Do you mind?
来吧
Let's do this.
好了 大家听着
Okay, people, listen up.
不管今天发生什么 弗兰肯斯坦都不会赢
Whatever happens today, Frankenstein cannot win.
睁大你们的眼睛
So, keep your eyes open.
欢迎来到死亡飞车赛的最后一站
Welcome to the final stage of Death Race.
所有的目光都投向一个人
All eyes are on one man.
弗兰肯斯坦 他是飞车赛史上最有实力的车手
Frankenstein. He's been the most dominant driver in Death Race history.
他能否再坚持一天 并赢得他的自由呢?
But can he hold on for one more day and win to earn his freedom?
点燃这些婊子们
Torch these bitches.
让你的心和直觉指引你
Let your heart and gut guide you.
你能做到 你能做到
You can do this. You can do this.
卢克 小心第三个弯道 是个急弯
Luke, watch out for turn three. It's a massive turn.
我不喜欢这个音乐
I don't like this music.
能放点别的吗? 天啊 我讨厌这音乐
Can you get something else? God, I hate this music.
非常好 棒极了
Yeah, that's nice. Yes.
在车手们到达红石路时
Frankenstein continues to hold a slim lead,
弗兰肯斯坦仍保持微弱的领先优势
as the drivers reach Red Rock Road.
离开这个区域 武器必须重新激活
Leaving sector. Weapons must be reactivated.
武器标记快到了
Weapons marker coming up.
来吧 好好玩玩 狗娘养的
Come on, play nice, motherfucker.
稳住 卡特里娜 我受够这家伙了
Hang on, Katrina. I've had enough of this guy.
坐稳
Hold on.
耶? 非常好
Yeah? It's nice.
再见 朋友
Adios amigo.
酷!出局
Cool. Get out!
你个野种 罗斯 我还为你活着呢!
You bastard, Razor! I'm still alive and coming for you!
不!
No!
水 救命 救我 水
Water! Help! Help me! Water.
疯子死了 就只剩下弗兰克,
The Psycho's death leaves only Frankenstein,
14K 和罗斯还在比赛
14K and Razor left alive to compete.
参赛者们进入了采石场 直通终点站
The racers enter the quarry, heading to the finish line.
弗兰肯斯坦刚得到武器 在第一位 就要赢了
Frankenstein just got weapons, and he's in the lead, about to win.
他心知肚明
He's gonna need more than that.
导弹就位
Ready the missiles.
你要在全世界人的关注下杀弗兰肯斯坦
You wanna kill Frankenstein while the whole world watches,
观众们不会放过你的
the audience will never forgive you.
你会毁掉这个秀
You will kill the fucking show.
这是我自己的事!
It is mine to fucking kill!
目标锁定
Target's locked.
他就要接近终点线了
He's too close to the finish line.
你会杀死很多人的
You could kill dozens of people.
你懂什么 普鲁登斯 你说得对 你总是说得对
You know what, Prudence? You're right. You're always right.
你令人讨厌
You're fired.
你还在这做啥? 滚出我的视线!
You're still here? Get out of my sight now!
好的
Okay.
开火
Fire.
嘿 伙计们 团结起来吧
Hey, guys. Get ready for some company.
该死
Shit.
是跟踪装置
It's the tracking device.
哦 操
Oh, fuck.
- 什么?  - 激活对策!
- What? - Activate countermeasures!
我们过不了这一关
We're not gonna make it through this.
哦  该死
Oh, shit.
激活了
Activated.
开火!
Fire!
没门儿
No way.
别他妈的做梦了!
No fucking way!
你有几条命?
How many lives do you have?
嗯  至少有一条
Well, at least one more, I guess.
他是怎么活下来的?
How the fuck did he survive that?
你跟我说的跟踪装置非常可靠
You told me that tracking device was foolproof.
是谁设计的?
Who designed it?
你的同伴
Your company did.
嘿 雷斯特 帮我跟14K连线
Hey, Lists. Patch me through to 14K's rig.
跟14K连线
Patch me through to 14K.
- 你来 - 好了吗?
- You're up. - You got him?
你和14K连上了
You're on with 14K, Luke.
嘿, 14K
Hey, 14K.
谢了不客气
Thank you. You're welcome.
我们都走到现在了
We're even now,
卢卡斯
Lucas.
- 准备好了吗?  - 我们把这完成吧
- Are you ready? - Let's finish this.
我是来杀你的
I'm coming to kill you.
你听得到吗 奈尔?
You hear me, Niles?
我来杀了你
I'm coming to kill you.
亲自来杀你的 听到了吗 奈尔斯?
Personally coming to kill you. You hear me, Niles?
打开麦克 打开所有的麦克!
Open all mics. Open all mics!
注意，警卫
Attention, guards.
弗兰肯斯坦第一个冲过终点 拿下他!
Frankenstein is headed to the finish line. Take him out!
你个懦夫
You're such a coward.
出去 出去!
Out, out!
你说得对 他背叛我了
You were right. He screwed me over.
我真该听你的 我该怎么做?
I should have listened to you before. What do you want me to do?
来吧!
Come on!
干掉他!
Take him out!
来吧 射他!
Come on, shoot him!
来吧!
Come on!
操!
Fuck!
你要去哪里?
Where do you think you're going?
你认为我会让一个二逼毁掉我所建立的一切吗?
You think I'm gonna let a simple fucking con ruin everything that I've built?
弗兰肯斯坦直通向终点
Frankenstein has a clear path to the finish.
他就快赢了
He's about to win.
14K超越了弗兰肯斯坦 越过了终点线
14K pulls past Frankenstein and crosses the finish line.
太好了!
Fuck yeah!
14K 赢得了死亡飞车赛
14k wins the Death Race.
你能赢的
You could've won that.
我知道 这不再是一场与胜利有关的比赛了
I know. It's not about winning races anymore.
他输了 一切都完了
He lost. It's over.
没比赛了
No more games.
我不会那么说
I wouldn't say that.
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
是的 我准备好了
Yeah, I'm ready.
我爱你
I love you.
看到了你的另一面
See you on the other side, kid.
我要亲自杀了他
I'm gonna take him out myself.
等等
Wait.
你哪也别想去
You aren't going anywhere.
他妈的怎么啦? 把钥匙给我
What the hell? Give me the fucking key!
这是你的成果 你接受它非常合适
This is your production. It's quite fitting that you go down with it.
松开这该死的鬼东西!
Get this fucking thing off me!
我非常遗憾地报道奈尔斯的死讯
It is my sad duty to announce the death of Niles York.
这位将死亡飞车赛带给我们梦幻的倡导者
The visionary entrepreneur who brought Death Race to us,
在爆炸中身亡 同时卡特里娜·班克斯
died in an explosion that also claimed the life of Katrina Banks
在最终的角逐中赢得了第三
on this third and final day of competition.
我们对奈尔斯的家人和朋友表示深深的同情
We'd like to extend our deepest sympathies to Mr. York's family and friends.
还有人活着!
Someone's alive!
是弗兰肯斯坦吗?
Is this really Frankenstein?
是的 是弗兰肯斯坦
Yes. Yes, it is Frankenstein.
跟踪装置已确认
The tracking device confirms it.
是的 是的 我确信弗兰肯斯坦还活着
Yes, yes. I can confirm that Frankenstein has survived
现在正赶回终极岛
and is currently en route back to Terminal Island.
我把重建死亡飞车赛的任务交到你手里
I leave the task of rebuilding Death Race in your very capable hands.
死亡飞车赛的家在终极岛
Death Race's home is Terminal Island.
不是其他地方
Nowhere else.
我为弗兰肯斯坦安排了新的后勤人员
I've arranged a new pit crew leader for Frankenstein.
你该提前收集他的资料
You should have his information in front of you.
是的 是的 那当然好
Yes, yes, that's all well and good.
但是弗兰肯斯坦呢?
But what of Frankenstein?
消息称弗兰肯斯坦思维敏捷
I've been informed that Frankenstein is alert,
意识好 还会提前两周为比赛做准备
conscious, and will be ready to race in two weeks.
对不起 等下
Excuse me for a minute.
怎么了?
What happened?
他一醒来就大叫 还胡说八道
He just woke up screaming, rambling a bunch of nonsense.
我不是弗兰肯斯坦!
I'm not Frankenstein!
他明显还处于休克中
He's obviously still in shock.
我们让他的朋友把他平静下来
We brought his friend down to calm him down.
弗兰克?
Frank?
我他妈的最后再说一次
For the last fucking time,
我不是弗兰肯斯坦
I am not Frankenstein.
这么说你非常确定?
So you're absolutely sure?
是他 我从来没见过他那样
It's him all right. But I've never seen him like that before.
普鲁登斯 告诉他们 告诉他们我是谁 我是奈尔斯
Prudence, tell them. Tell them who I am. I'm Niles York.
我不是弗兰肯斯坦!
I am not Frankenstein!
不是!
No!
嘿 宝贝儿
Hello, baby.
一切还好吗?
Is everything okay?
不是还好
No.
应该是完美
It's perfect.
好的 爱人
All right, lovebirds.
你总是值得依靠
We can always rely on you.
- 敬雷斯特  - 敬雷斯特
- To Lists. - To Lists.
你收到我的邮件了吗?
Did you get my wire?
嗯 我现在正在看呢 非常...
Yeah, I'm looking at it right now. It's very...
非常丰厚  谢谢你
Very generous. Thank you.
就你所做的 我三倍奉还
For what you did to that bastard, I would have paid triple.
嗯 如果我知道的话
Well, if I'd known that.
我的计划就是杀了他
I thought the plan was to kill him.
情况变了
Well, things change, huh?
就我而言 我想我做的比杀了他更好
Personally, I think I did better than that.
- 你是在抱怨吗?   - 不是
- Are you complaining? - Hell, no.
你是怎么完成的?
How the hell did you pull it off?
那个混蛋欺骗了你 是吗?
That son of a bitch screwed you over, didn't he?
我们做这个 有个条件
We do this, one condition.
我和那家伙有个协议
I made a deal with the guy.
你输就活 赢就死
You lose, you live. You win, you die.
这事你们都该知道
There's something you all need to know.
我签了协议
I did make a deal.
做了个交易
With our old boss.
韦兰?
Weyland?
我希望他能重新协定 但是他不愿意
And I expected him to at least renegotiate. But he didn't.
别小看他
Do not underestimate him.
他在预谋一些事情
He's planning something.
我的路 我的原则 我的计划
My way, my rules, my plan.
我有非常重要的事情要跟你们说
I'm gonna need something very important from you.
是什么?
And what's that?
我要杀了你 高博
I'm gonna need to kill you, Goldberg.
他们是卡拉哈里的军阀
They're the warlords of Kalahari.
听着 我会把军阀带入比赛
Look, I'm gonna bring these warlords into the race.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
谁要做什么?
What's who doing?
当大家都在看比赛的时候 我要你退出比赛
While everybody's watching, I'm gonna need you to take yourself out.
我需要一个信号
I'm gonna need a signal.
那儿会非常喧闹
It's gonna be loud.
你要我做什么?
What do you need me to do?
我们需要一个知情人
We need someone on the inside.
去做吧
Done.
危险已过
The coast is clear.
皮斯的死我非常抱歉
I'm sorry to hear about that dead spic.
这是我的成果
This is my production.
你说得对
You were right.
出去 出去!
Out, out!
他背叛了我
He screwed me over.
我应该听你的话
I should have listened to you before.
弗兰肯斯坦冲过终点线 干掉他!
Frankenstein is headed to the finish line. Take him out!
帮帮你自己 现在听我说
Do yourself a favor and listen to me right now.
我会亲自干掉他
I'm gonna take him out myself.
你要我做什么?
What do you want me to do?
无论如何 让他呆在房间里
Keep him in the room. No matter what.
这该死的钥匙!
The fucking key!
死亡飞车赛有着终极奖励
Death Race has the ultimate prize.
赢得你的自由
You win your freedom.
这一切都是弗兰肯斯坦造成的
This all starts and ends with Frankenstein.
有人还活着!
Someone's alive!
我就是想知道
I was just wondering
你是不是原版的弗兰肯斯坦
if you are the original Frankenstein.
是的 是弗兰肯斯坦
Yes, it is Frankenstein.
跟踪装置确认了他
The tracking device confirms it.
弗兰肯斯坦永生
Frankenstein can never die.
他会被枪击 他会玉石俱焚 他会爆炸
He can be shot. He can crash and burn. He can explode.
但是弗兰肯斯坦总是能摆脱困境
But Frankenstein will always emerge.
弗兰肯斯坦 他是死亡飞车
Frankenstein, he is Death Race.
卡尔·卢卡斯 也许他安息了
Carl Lucas, may he rest in peace.
嗯 危险解除
Psst! The coast is clear.
我不走
I'm not going.
你说你不走是什么意思? 你必须走
What are you talking about you're not going? You have to.
离开这儿我没一点好处
I was never any good out there.
我不明白规则
I didn't understand the rules.
在监狱里 一切才有意义
In prison, things make sense.
嗯 还有 有人必须留下来
And, plus, someone has to stay behind.
一位目击者讲述着悲惨故事
A witness to tell the tale.
你做的不和逻辑
What you're doing isn't logical.
对 他是对的
Yeah, he's right.
有人曾经告诉我
Someone once told me,
去他妈的逻辑
fuck logic.
跟着你的心走
Let your heart tell you what's right.
我和韦兰谈过 我来这儿是帮你的
I spoke to Weyland. I'm here to help you.
蓝图 电气系统 通风井
Blueprints, electrical systems, ventilation shafts.
现在 没有大牌明星
Now, how would your little copycat event play
你怎么玩转山寨游戏?
without the game's marquee star?
带着面具的人
It's a man in a mask.
粉丝们怎么知道哪一个是真的?
How would the fans know which one was real?
那就是你失败的原因
That's why you're going to fail.
那家伙想成为百万富翁 将来会成为笑柄
The boy wonder billionaire will become the laughing stock.
你所知所爱的死亡飞车不会改变
The Death Race that you all know and love will not change.
他将越发壮大 这一点 我保证
It will grow bigger and better. This, I promise.
现在 如果你突然改变规则
Now, if you suddenly change the rules of the game,
你将会失去你的观众
you're going to lose your audience.
你要做什么 替换掉我 用谁?
What are you gonna do, replace me? With who?
扯蛋的回报 小子
Payback's a bitch, son.
我是弗兰肯斯坦
I am Frankenstein.
我会复仇的
And I will have my revenge.